linksearching.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy – LinkSearching

This privacy policy manages the ways how **LinkSearching.com** collects, uses, maintains and discloses information gathered from the users (a user of **linksearching.com** ). This privacy policy is applicable to the all information, services and products provided by **linksearching.com**.

### Personal Identification Information

We may collect the personal identification data from the users in various ways like, when users visit and register our site, give an order, subscribe to the newsletters, fill out a form, and connect with other services, resources, activities, or features that are having our site. The users may be asked, as the manner, for name, email address, mailing address, or credit card data. We gather their personal identification information only if they give us willingly. The users have right to deny submitting their personal information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in particular site related to activities.

### Non-Personal Identification Information

We collect non-personal identification information from the users when they interact with our site. The non-personal information may be browser name, internet provider, internet type, computer operating system etc.

### Cookies

We may use the user website’s cookies to beautify their web experiences. The web browser of users reserve cookies on the hard drive for the purpose of record keeping and often tracking information on them. User may set their browsers to deny cookies or to alert you during cookies are being sent. If they do really so, some of the functions of the site may not work right.

### How We Use Collected Information

**Linksearching.com** uses the user’s personal identification data for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service
  * To personalize the user experience
  * To improve our site
  * To process easy payments
  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

### How We Protect Your Information

We manage a secured data stored function. We collect, store and process information in the safest ways against all vulnerabilities. We protect your data against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### How We Share User’s Personal Data

We do not share, sell, rent or trade the user’s personal information to the 3rd parties. We may only share generic aggregated demographic information that is not related to any personal identification information about the users and visitors with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes described above. We may use the service of 3rd party providers to assist us to run our business, the site or administrative functions on our behalf like sending out surveys or newsletters. We may provide your information to the 3rd parties in limited purposes if you only give us permission.

### Privacy Policy Changing

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy, if we need. When we do so, we will inform you via email. It is your responsibility to be informed with the update of privacy policy periodically. If any loss you face by changing privacy policy, it is your responsibility to handle it.

### Your Acceptance of Privacy Policy

By using this site, you agree to this privacy policy. If you do not agree, don’t use this site. Your continuous use of this site is meant that you are updated with the change of this privacy policy.

If you have any question about this privacy policy, you can contact us.
